{
    "subject": "resource/Techno_Cumbia",
    "predicate": "property/label",
    "object": "resource/Capitol_Latin",
    "human_readable": "The label of Techno Cumbia is Capitol Latin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9699320793151855,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Techno Cumbia and Capitol Latin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8145965933799744,
            "question": "What genre label is associated with Capitol Latin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6191866993904114,
            "question": "Give an example of a music label that uses the term 'Capitol Latin'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5046384930610657,
            "question": "What kind of music might be considered 'Capitol Latin'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4449044167995453,
            "question": "What musical style is Capitol Latin associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41516196727752686,
            "question": "What does 'Capitol Latin' refer to in music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34972262382507324,
            "question": "What is the term used to describe Techno Cumbia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3485664129257202,
            "question": "Can you name a music genre that falls under Capitol Latin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.278658390045166,
            "question": "Is Techno Cumbia a type of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25277236104011536,
            "question": "How would you describe the musical genre of Techno Cumbia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Techno Cumbia is Capitol Latin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1908_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Techno Cumbia a type of music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1908_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a music genre that falls under Capitol Latin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1908_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the term used to describe Techno Cumbia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1908_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1908_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1908_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1908_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1908_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1908_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1908_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1908_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1908_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1908_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1908_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention any information about the label of Techno Cumbia being Capitol Latin. Therefore, the statement is not supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no mention nor evidence in the context information suggesting that the label of Techno Cumbia is Capitol Latin. Instead, it mentions various independent record labels like Music Garden Records, Minimalistic Art Records, Casa Del Puente Discos, Alma-Electronica, Castelar Discos, Static Discos, and Abolipop Records from different countries in Latin America that specialize in Techno Cumbia. Therefore, the label is not Capitol Latin as stated in the claim.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of a label called \"Capitol Latin\" associated with Techno Cumbia in the provided text.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There are multiple labels associated with the Techno Cumbia movement across Latin America, such as ZZK Records, Salviatek, and Castelar Discos, among others, but there is no singular label called \"Capitol Latin\" that represents the entire genre.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context does not mention Capitol Latin as a label for Techno Cumbia. Instead, it highlights several independent labels such as Music Garden Records, Minimalistic Art Records, Casa Del Puente Discos, Alma-Electronica, Castelar Discos, Static Discos and Abolipop Records that are associated with the Latin electronic scene, including elements of techno cumbia.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}